[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which statement below, concerning even numbers, is true?", "correct_answer": "There are no even irrational numbers", "incorrect_answers": ["There are no even cardinal numbers", "There are no even prime numbers", "There are no even perfect numbers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Though this action movie takes place in Egypt, it couldnt be shot in Egypt due to the countrys unstable political conditions.", "correct_answer": "The Mummy", "incorrect_answers": ["Walking Across Egypt", "Three Kings", "The 13th Warrior"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How many genes does the human DNA contain?", "correct_answer": "About 80 000", "incorrect_answers": ["About 200 000", "About 8 000", "About 20 000"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What was the special speaker system used during the 1974 theatrical release of the movie Earthquake?", "correct_answer": "Sensurround", "incorrect_answers": ["Tremor speaker simulators", "Seismaseats", "Tremorsound"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What does a convex mirror do?", "correct_answer": "It deceases the size", "incorrect_answers": ["It increases the size", "None of these", "It widens the size."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year did the horror flick An American Werewolf in London come out?", "correct_answer": "1981", "incorrect_answers": ["1980", "1983", "1986"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Orlons had a 1963 hit in which they told everyone where all the hippies meet. Where was this, according to the song?", "correct_answer": "South Street", "incorrect_answers": ["San Francisco", "Greenwich Village", "State Street"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Ramones recorded the title song to which Stephen King film?", "correct_answer": "Pet Semetary", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dead Zone", "Creepshow", "Salems Lot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The nature of what animal does Buddy Love have in the 2000 comedy Nutty Professor II: The Klumps?", "correct_answer": "Dog", "incorrect_answers": ["Fish", "Hamster", "Cat"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which woodwind instrument is not made of wood and has no reeds?", "correct_answer": "Flute", "incorrect_answers": ["Clarinet", "Oboe", "Accordion"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what Arab country did the Sangak bread variety originate?", "correct_answer": "Iran", "incorrect_answers": ["Libya", "Iraq", "Morocco"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Add 20 to 30 drops of essential oil to a 100ml bottle of spring or deionized water and leave it in a dark space for a few days. Then filter it to make this.", "correct_answer": "Flower water", "incorrect_answers": ["Bath oil", "Skin oil", "Cold compress"]}]